Oh.
A thousand miles of winter grey Another dawn,
another day The engines hum, a weary soul A heavy
price, a heavy toll I see your face on frozen
glass A memory that's built to last A single
light that I must find To leave the endless dark
behind
And the lights are bright on this winter's night
Because you're coming home Yes, you're finally
coming home Through the wind and rain Through
the doubt and pain You are not alone No, you're
finally coming home
The towns fly by a blur of light I count the hours
in the night Remembering a whispered vow It
feels so close, it's coming now The fire's lit,
the table's set A promise that I haven't met But
in my heart the feeling grows The warmth that
melts the winter snows
And the lights are bright on this winter's night
Because you're coming home Yes, you're finally
coming home Through the wind and rain Through
the doubt and pain You are not alone No, you're
finally coming home
you
And the lights are bright on this winter's night
Because you're coming home Yes, you're finally
coming home Through the wind and rain Through
the doubt and pain You are not alone Know you're
finally coming
home
Coming home
On this day
you.